https://www.pinalcentral.com/site/privacy.html

COVID-19
Privacy PolicyCasa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc. / PinalCentral.com Privacy PolicyCasa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc. / PinalCentral.com (“us”, “our” or “we”) want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you because we understand you are concerned about your privacy, and we want to maintain your trust. This Privacy Notice discloses the privacy practices of our website, whether accessed through a computer, tablet, smartphone or other device (individually or collectively, “Device” or “Devices”). We believe in your right to know what information is collected during your visit to our website ("Services"), and to any Services that display this notice and how that information is used and safeguarded.Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using this website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.Information Automatically Gathered About All VisitorsWe collect aggregate and user-specific information on which pages consumers access or visit. This information is used to generate reports that help us assess the value of and interest in the various website sections and Services we provide. We use the information we collect to improve the content of our Services. We can build a better site and provide better Services if we know which pages our users are visiting, how often they visit and how long they stay on a page.Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address (but not the e-mail address), when you utilize our Services. Your IP address does not contain personally identifiable information, nor does it identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our Services to you upon request, to tailor our sites and Services to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our sites.To help make our Services more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we may utilize a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of computer code that is deposited on your hard drive by our site. Browsers typically recognize when a cookie has been sent to your computer and give you the option to refuse or allow it. A cookie does not actually identify you, just the computer or device that you are using to access our Services. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers, content partners and Services that are reached from links on our Services may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we cannot control.We use cookies to help us tailor our Services to your needs so we can deliver a better and more personalized Services. It is a cookie, for example, that allows us to deliver to you any personalized information each time you visit our Services.In addition, we can access cookies later in your current session or in a later session on our Services in order to improve your visit to our Services, as in the following examples:Social MediaWe may provide you the option to connect your account on the Website to your account on some social networking sites for the purpose of logging in, uploading information or enabling certain features on the Website. When logging in using your social network credentials, we may collect the Personally-Identifying Information you have made publicly available on the social networking site, such as your name, profile picture, cover photo, username, gender, friends network, age range, locale, friend list and any other information you have made public. Once connected, other users may also be able to see information about your social network, such as the size of your network and your friends, including common friends. By connecting your account on the Website to your account on any social networking site, you hereby consent to the continuous release of information about you to us. We will not send any of your account information to the connected social networking site without first disclosing that to you. Each social network may further allow you to set privacy controls around your information on their system, and our collection of information will always follow such controls and permissions. This feature is subject to continuous change and improvement by us and each social networking site involved, and therefore the available features and shared information are subject to change without notice to you.We may use hyperlinks on the Website which will redirect you to a social network if you click on the respective link. However, when you click on a social plug-in, such as Facebook’s “Like” button, Twitter’s “tweet” button or the Google+, that particular social network’s plugin will be activated and your browser will directly connect to that provider’s servers. If you do not use these buttons, none of your data will be sent to the respective social network’s plugin provider. So for example, when you click on the Facebook’s “Like” button on the Website, Facebook will receive your IP address, the browser version and screen resolution, and the operating system of the device you have used to access the Website. Settings regarding privacy protection can be found on the websites of these social networks and are not within our control.Account RegistrationIf your use of a component of the Services requires you to register, a cookie will be used to automatically identify you as a registered user when you are using our Services. These cookies are known as persistent cookies and continue on your computer after the initial session in which they are created.This cookie allows us to maintain information containing the products (like photo reprints) or Services (such as placing a classified advertisement or signing up for home delivery) you are purchasing while you are online. To limit unauthorized access, this cookie, also called a session cookie, expires whenever you exit a browser session.Like many other commercial sites, our Services may utilize an electronic file called a web beacon to count users who have visited a page or to recognize users by accessing certain cookies. Our Services and/or our partner websites use web beacons for auditing purposes and to collect information from the websites and Services of certain partners. Information recorded through these web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users from our partners. Aggregate information may include demographic and usage information. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with partners. To opt-out of a third parties’ use of web beacons please click here.Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar MechanismsSome browsers or other tools include “Do Not Track” (DNT) features which, when turned on, send a signal to websites you visit indicating that you do not wish to be tracked across websites over time. The Worldwide Web Consortium (W3C) has been working with industry groups and regulators to develop a DNT browser technology standard to provide a common understanding as to how to interpret the DNT signals, but to date no standard has been adopted. Since there is no standard at this time, we do not currently respond to DNT signals. We will follow the progress of the W3C in developing the standard. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.California Privacy RightsCalifornia Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about the Personally-Identifying Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of the Personally-Identifying Information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared Personally-Identifying Information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us as listed below. Prohibited UsesThis Site is not intended for use by persons located within the European Economic Area (EEA). We do not request or accept personal information concerning or supplied by persons who are located within the EEA at the time they access this Site. If you have accessed this Site from within the EEA, you should immediately discontinue your use. If you have supplied personal information to us in violation of this provision, whether through the registration of new user accounts or otherwise, please contact us at web@pinalcentral.com.Advertising PolicyAll Classified and Online ads are subject to the applicable rate card, copies of which are available from our Advertising Department. All ads are subject to approval before publication. Casa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc. reserves the right to edit, refuse, reject, classify or cancel any ad at any time. Errors must be reported in the first day of publication. Casa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc. shall not be liable for any loss or expense that result from an error in or omission of an advertisement.No refunds for early cancellation of order.SubscriptionWe may offer some of our Services on a subscription basis. By subscribing to any such Services, you authorize us to charge your credit card or debit card an initial payment at the time of signing up, and a regular recurring payment may take place on the next billing day of your billing cycle. Applicable sales tax included. Prices subject to change during term. After promotional offers conclude, your subscription will continue at the regular rate until we are otherwise notified. By supplying your e-mail address you are authorizing us to send you future promotional offers and discounts. Subscriptions are available as EasyPay. Your credit or debit card will be automatically charged every renewal period until you notify us otherwise. You are responsible for any recurring charges that take place prior to cancellation. ClassifiedsThese rates are available only by placing your ad through the self serve site and may differ from calling into our classified sales center.All orders are pre-paid by credit card only. Due to the type of advertising sold online, no pro-rated refunds or discounts will be made for any ad cancelled following the first publication. About Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our Services. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our site in order to provide advertisements about goods and Services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer website.Google Doubleclick for Publishers (DFP) is an ad network partner that displays ads on our Services. To improve your ad experience on our sites and Services and elsewhere on the Internet, we may send non-personal information to Google DFP based on your browser's activities, such as type of pages viewed and categories of interests, so that the advertising you see is relevant to you. Google DFP also may use information regarding its own users to select which ads to display. Click here to learn more about Google DFP's ad practices, including how to opt out of using anonymous information to select which ads to show you.Opt-Out of CookiesIf you wish to manage or opt-out of cookies utilized by our site and third party advertisers, you can take the following steps:You may be able to download an opt-out cookie from the third party advertiser’s website allowing you to opt-out of cookies. Please visit the third party advertiser’s websites for more information.Your web browser may allow you to manage what cookies are accepted or declined. These settings can usually be found in the preferences or options menus of your web browser.Your web browser may also allow you to manually view cookies and delete the cookies you don’t want or need. Check your web browser’s settings for more information.Websites that require registration may allow you to opt-out of cookies. Check the account settings or preferences section of the website for more information.For more information, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. Information Gathered by Voluntary SubmissionTo make use of certain features on our Services (such as contests, story comments, letters to the editor, personalized web pages and other interactive forums and blogs) visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration or participation process. We may ask, for example, for your name, e-mail address, gender, age, and zip code, and we might request information on your interest in sports, personal finance, the performing arts, and the like.The information you supply will help us offer you more personalized features, to tailor our Services to your interests and make them more useful to you. The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you do not supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with Services and content we make available to other visitors to our Services. Of course, even if you want to remain completely anonymous, you are still free to take advantage of the wealth of content that is otherwise available, without registration, in using our Services.Children under the Age of 13If you are under the age of 13, do not send us any information about yourself such as your name, address or e-mail address. You may only send us personally identifiable information if your parents have verified to us their consent to the collection of the information.Because we are a media company, some of our online Services and content may be attractive to children. Because we strive to protect the privacy of all users of our Services, including children, we endeavor to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Our site:Includes our contact information.Explains the types of personal information we collect, and how we use it.Explains our practices in terms of sharing personal information with third parties.Allows parents to consent to the collection and use of their children’s personal information, without consenting to disclosure to third parties.Does not condition a child’s participation in an activity on the child’s providing more personal information than is reasonably necessary for the activity.Allows parents to review their child’s information, have it deleted, or refuse to permit any further collection, by contacting us.We make a special effort to encourage children under the age of 13 to consult with their parents before furnishing any personal data. However, we also believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online Services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental permission.E-mails from UsUpon registering with our Services, you may begin receiving communications from us. In addition, if you have signed up for any of our automated account Services, we will send you transactional e-mails regarding the status of your account, including confirmations, notices of expiration and renewal and other related electronic correspondence. If you have signed up for any of our e-mail newsletters, you may stop receiving them if you follow the "unsubscribe" instructions located near the bottom of each newsletter. We may send you an e-mail inviting you to participate in subscriber or website user surveys. Such surveys greatly help us improve our Services and the value of our websites. Any information you give us in those surveys will not be shared with any third parties except in aggregate form.What We Do With the Information We Gather About YouWe or one of our affiliated companies may perform statistical, marketing and demographic analyses of our delivery subscribers and their subscription patterns. In addition, we may generally inform our advertisers about our subscriber base. When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our sites. We will not share individual user information with third parties unless the user has specifically approved the release of that information; however, in some cases, we may provide information to legal officials as described in “Compliance with Legal Process” below. Further, please note that if Casa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc., or any of its subsidiaries or lines of business is merged, acquired, divested, financed, sold, disposed of or dissolved, including through merger of, consolidation, sale or divestiture of assets, the relevant customer database, including personally identifiable information we may possess about you, may, in whole or in part, be sold, disposed of, transferred, divested, or otherwise disclosed as part of that transaction or proceeding.In addition, in some cases, we contract with third parties to provide Services on our behalf, including credit-card and bill processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, list processing and analytics or promotions management. We provide these third parties only with the information necessary for them to perform their specific Services. These Services providers are restricted from using this information in any way other than to provide Services to us, and they may not share this information with anyone else nor may they resell this data.Compliance with Legal ProcessWe may disclose personal information if we or one of our affiliated companies is required by law to disclose personal information, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to comply with a law or some legal process, to protect or defend our rights and property, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Services or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.A Final Note:We are affiliated with other online companies, some of which feature our branding; in addition there are numerous links to third parties contained on our site. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to those companies' websites, so you should refer to each of those sites to obtain information on their privacy policies. If you cannot find the privacy policy on any of these sites once you have arrived at their site via a link from our site, you should contact that site directly for more information.The web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect if we believe that the change in the way we use your personal information is significant or material. Of course, our use of information gathered while the current policy is in effect will always be consistent with the current policy, even if we change that policy later.ContactCasa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc.PinalCentral.com/Privacy Policy200 W. 2nd St.Casa Grande, AZ 85122(520) 836-7461web@pinalcentral.com
Trending
Woman arrested for attempted robbery of CG auto parts store
Man dies after becoming entangled in drill rig in Hidden Valley
Stonegate development along Maricopa-Casa Grande Highway moves forward
Helen’s Kitchen and Catering has new storefront
Former Florence prison guard pleads guilty to aggravated assault
TriValley Trending Businesses
©Copyright 2020 Casa Grande Valley Newspapers Inc., a division of Kramer Media, 200 W. 2nd St. Casa Grande, AZ | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
